<SATWordList>
<SATWord>
<word>Amenity
</word>
<def>an agreeable way or manner; courtesy; civility: the graceful amenities of society.</def>
<pron>a·men·i·ty</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Aperture
</word>
<def>an opening, as a hole, slit, crack, gap, etc.</def>
<pron>ap·er·ture</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Dissidence
</word>
<def>Protest against official policy; dissent</def>
<pron>dis·si·dence</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Epicurean
</word>
<def>fond of or adapted to luxury or indulgence in sensual pleasures; having luxurious tastes or habits, especially in eating and drinking.</def>
<pron>ep·i·cu·re·an</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Improvident
</word>
<def>not provident; lacking foresight; incautious; unwary.</def>
<pron>im·prov·i·dent</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Iniquity
</word>
<def>Immoral or grossly unfair behavior. (injustice) </def>
<pron>in·iq·ui·ty</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Inviolable
</word>
<def>prohibiting violation; secure from destruction, violence, infringement, or desecration: an inviolable sanctuary; an inviolable promise.</def>
<pron>in·vi·o·la·ble</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Mutable
</word>
<def>liable or subject to change or alteration.</def>
<pron>mu·ta·ble</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Nascent
</word>
<def>beginning to exist or develop: the nascent republic.</def>
<pron>nas·cent</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Obeisance
</word>
<def>a movement of the body expressing deep respect or deferential courtesy, as before a superior; a bow, curtsy, or other similar gesture.</def>
<pron>o·bei·sance</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Panegyric
</word>
<def>a lofty oration or writing in praise of a person or thing; eulogy.</def>
<pron>pan·e·gyr·ic</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Pillory
</word>
<def>a wooden framework erected on a post, with holes for securing the head and hands, formerly used to expose an offender to public derision.</def>
<pron>pil·lo·ry</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Pittance
</word>
<def>a small amount or share.</def>
<pron>pit·tance</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Presage
</word>
<def>a presentiment or foreboding.</def>
<pron>pres·age</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Progeny
</word>
<def>a descendant or offspring, as a child, plant, or animal.</def>
<pron>prog·e·ny</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Promulgate
</word>
<def>to make known by open declaration; publish; proclaim formally or put into operation (a law, decree of a court, etc.).</def>
<pron>prom·ul·gate</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Rectitude
</word>
<def>rightness of principle or conduct; moral virtue: the rectitude of her motives.</def>
<pron>rec·ti·tude</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Restive
</word>
<def>impatient of control, restraint, or delay, as persons; restless; uneasy.</def>
<pron>res·tive</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Seraphic
</word>
<def>Angelic</def>
<pron>se·raph·ic</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Subsist
</word>
<def>to exist; continue in existence.</def>
<pron>sub·sist</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Acquisitive
</word>
<def>Excessively interested in acquiring money or material things</def>
<pron>ac·quis·i·tive</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Arrogate
</word>
<def>Take or claim (something) for oneself without justification</def>
<pron>ar·ro·gate</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Banal
</word>
<def>So lacking in originality as to be obvious and boring.</def>
<pron>ba·nal</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Belabor
</word>
<def>Argue or elaborate (a subject) in excessive detail: "they belabored the obvious".
    Attack or assault (someone) physically or verbally.</def>
<pron>be·la·bor</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Carping
</word>
<def>characterized by fussy or petulant faultfinding; querulous: carping criticism.</def>
<pron>carp·ing</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Coherent
</word>
<def>logically connected; consistent: a coherent argument.</def>
<pron>co·her·ent</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Congeal
</word>
<def>to change from a soft or fluid state to a rigid or solid state, as by cooling or freezing: The fat congealed on the top of the soup.</def>
<pron>con·geal</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Emulate
</word>
<def>to try to equal or excel; imitate with effort to equal or surpass: to emulate one's father as a concert violinist.</def>
<pron>em·u·late</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Encomium
</word>
<def>A speech or piece of writing that praises someone or something highly.</def>
<pron>en·co·mi·um</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Eschew
</word>
<def>Deliberately avoid using; abstain from: "he appealed to the crowd to eschew violence".</def>
<pron>es·chew</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Germane
</word>
<def>closely or significantly related; relevant; pertinent: Please keep your statements germane to the issue.</def>
<pron>ger·mane</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Insatiable
</word>
<def>(of an appetite or desire) Impossible to satisfy: "an insatiable hunger"</def>
<pron>in·sa·tia·ble</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Intransigent
</word>
<def>refusing to agree or compromise; uncompromising; inflexible.</def>
<pron>in·tran·si·gent</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Invidious
</word>
<def>calculated to create ill will or resentment or give offense; hateful: invidious remarks.</def>
<pron>in·vid·i·ous</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Largesse
</word>
<def>generous bestowal of gifts.</def>
<pron>lar·gess</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Reconnaissance
</word>
<def>the act of reconnoitering.</def>
<pron>re·con·nais·sance</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Substantiate
</word>
<def>to establish by proof or competent evidence: to substantiate a charge.</def>
<pron>sub·stan·ti·ate</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Taciturn
</word>
<def>inclined to silence; reserved in speech; reluctant to join in conversation.</def>
<pron>tac·i·turn</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Temporize
</word>
<def>to be indecisive or evasive to gain time or delay acting.</def>
<pron>tem·po·rize</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Tenable
</word>
<def>capable of being held, maintained, or defended, as against attack or dispute: a tenable theory.</def>
<pron>ten·a·ble</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Accost
</word>
<def>to confront boldly: The beggar accosted me for money.</def>
<pron>ac·cost</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Animadversion
</word>
<def>an unfavorable or censorious comment: to make animadversions on someone's conduct.</def>
<pron>an·i·mad·ver·sion</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Avid
</word>
<def>showing great enthusiasm for or interest in: an avid moviegoer. Synonyms: enthusiastic, ardent, keen; devoted, dedicated; zealous, fanatic. Antonyms: indifferent, apathetic; reluctant.</def>
<pron>av·id</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Brackish
</word>
<def>slightly salt; having a salty or briny flavor.</def>
<pron>brack·ish</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Celerity
</word>
<def>Swiftness of movement.
</def>
<pron>ce·ler·i·ty</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Devious
</word>
<def>departing from the most direct way; circuitous; indirect: a devious course.</def>
<pron>de·vi·ous</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Gambit
</word>
<def>A device, action, or opening remark, typically one entailing a degree of risk, that is calculated to gain an advantage.</def>
<pron>gam·bit</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Halcyon
</word>
<def>calm; peaceful; tranquil: halcyon weather.</def>
<pron>hal·cy·on</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Histrionic
</word>
<def>of or pertaining to actors or acting.</def>
<pron>his·tri·on·ic</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Incendiary
</word>
<def>used or adapted for setting property on fire: incendiary bombs.</def>
<pron>in·cen·di·ar·y</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Maelstrom
</word>
<def>a large, powerful, or violent whirlpool.</def>
<pron>mael·strom</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Myopic
</word>
<def>nearsighted: unable to see distant objects clearly</def>
<pron>my·op·ic</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Overt
</word>
<def>open to view or knowledge; not concealed or secret: overt hostility.</def>
<pron>o·vert</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Pejorative
</word>
<def>Expressing contempt or disapproval.</def>
<pron>pe·jo·ra·tive</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Propriety
</word>
<def>conformity to established standards of good or proper behavior or manners.</def>
<pron>pro·pri·e·ty</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Sacrilege
</word>
<def>the violation or profanation of anything sacred or held sacred.</def>
<pron>sac·ri·lege</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Summarily
</word>
<def>in a prompt or direct manner; immediately; straightaway.</def>
<pron>sum·mar·i·ly</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Suppliant
</word>
<def>a person who supplicates; petitioner.</def>
<pron>sup·pli·ant</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Talisman
</word>
<def>a stone, ring, or other object, engraved with figures or characters supposed to possess occult powers and worn as an amulet or charm.</def>
<pron>tal·is·man</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Undulate
</word>
<def>to move with a sinuous or wavelike motion; display a smooth rising-and-falling or side-to-side alternation of movement: The flag undulates in the breeze.</def>
<pron>un·du·late</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Articulate
</word>
<def>uttered clearly in distinct syllables.</def>
<pron>ar·tic·u·late</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Cavort
</word>
<def>Jump or dance around excitedly: "monkeys leap and cavort in the branches".
    Apply oneself to sexual or disreputable pursuits: "he spent his nights cavorting with the glitterati".</def>
<pron>ca·vort</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Credence
</word>
<def>belief as to the truth of something: to give credence to a claim.</def>
<pron>cre·dence</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Decry
</word>
<def>to speak disparagingly of; denounce as faulty or worthless; express censure of: She decried the lack of support for the arts in this country.</def>
<pron>de·cry</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Dissemble
</word>
<def>to give a false or misleading appearance to; conceal the truth or real nature of: to dissemble one's incompetence in business.</def>
<pron>dis·sem·ble</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Distraught
</word>
<def>distracted; deeply agitated.</def>
<pron>dis·traught</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Eulogy
</word>
<def>a speech or writing in praise of a person or thing, especially a set oration in honor of a deceased person.</def>
<pron>eu·lo·gy</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Evince
</word>
<def>to show clearly; make evident or manifest; prove.</def>
<pron>e·vince</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Exhume
</word>
<def>to dig (something buried, especially a dead body) out of the earth; disinter.</def>
<pron>ex·hume</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Feckless
</word>
<def>ineffective; incompetent; futile: feckless attempts to repair the plumbing.</def>
<pron>feck·less</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Murky
</word>
<def>dark, gloomy, and cheerless.</def>
<pron>murk·y</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Nefarious
</word>
<def>Wicked or criminal: "the nefarious activities of the organized-crime syndicates".</def>
<pron>ne·far·i·ous</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Piquant
</word>
<def>agreeably pungent or sharp in taste or flavor; pleasantly biting or tart: a piquant aspic.</def>
<pron>pi·quant</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Primordial
</word>
<def>constituting a beginning; giving origin to something derived or developed; original; elementary: primordial forms of life.</def>
<pron>pri·mor·di·al</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Propinquity
</word>
<def>nearness in place; proximity.</def>
<pron>pro·pin·qui·ty</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Unwonted
</word>
<def>not customary or usual; rare: unwonted kindness.</def>
<pron>un·wont·ed</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Utopian
</word>
<def>of, pertaining to, or resembling Utopia.</def>
<pron>U·to·pi·an</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Verbiage
</word>
<def>overabundance or superfluity of words, as in writing or speech; wordiness; verbosity.</def>
<pron>ver·bi·age</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Verdant
</word>
<def>green with vegetation; covered with growing plants or grass: a verdant oasis.</def>
<pron>ver·dant</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Viscous
</word>
<def>of a glutinous nature or consistency; sticky; thick; adhesive.</def>
<pron>vis·cous</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Atrophy
</word>
<def>A wasting away of the body or of an organ or part, as from defective nutrition or nerve damage.</def>
<pron>at·ro·phy</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Bastion
</word>
<def>Fortification. a projecting portion of a rampart or fortification that forms an irregular pentagon attached at the base to the main work.</def>
<pron>bas·tion</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Concord
</word>
<def>agreement between persons, groups, nations, etc.; concurrence in attitudes, feelings, etc.; unanimity; accord: There was complete concord among the delegates.</def>
<pron>con·cord</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Consummate
</word>
<def>to bring to a state of perfection; fulfill.</def>
<pron>con·sum·mate</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Disarray
</word>
<def>to put out of array or order; throw into disorder.</def>
<pron>dis·ar·ray</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Exigency
</word>
<def>exigent state or character; urgency.</def>
<pron>ex·i·gen·cy</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Flotsam
</word>
<def>the part of the wreckage of a ship and its cargo found floating on the water. People or things that have been rejected and are regarded as worthless.</def>
<pron>flot·sam</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Frenetic
</word>
<def>Fast and energetic in a rather wild and uncontrolled way: "a frenetic pace of activity"</def>
<pron>fre·net·ic</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Glean
</word>
<def>to gather slowly and laboriously, bit by bit.</def>
<pron>glean</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Grouse
</word>
<def>A grumble or complaint.</def>
<pron>grouse</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Incarcerate
</word>
<def>to imprison; confine.</def>
<pron>in·car·cer·ate</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Incumbent
</word>
<def>holding an indicated position, role, office, etc., currently: the incumbent officers of the club.</def>
<pron>in·cum·bent</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Jocular
</word>
<def>Fond of or characterized by joking; humorous or playful.
</def>
<pron>joc·u·lar</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Ludicrous
</word>
<def>So foolish, unreasonable, or out of place as to be amusing.</def>
<pron>lu·di·crous</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Mordant
</word>
<def>sharply caustic or sarcastic, as wit or a speaker; biting.</def>
<pron>mor·dant</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Nettle
</word>
<def>Irritate or annoy (someone): "I was nettled by her tone".
</def>
<pron>net·tle</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Pecuniary
</word>
<def>of or pertaining to money: pecuniary difficulties.</def>
<pron>pe·cu·ni·ar·y</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Pusillanimous
</word>
<def>lacking courage or resolution; cowardly; faint-hearted; timid.</def>
<pron>pu·sil·lan·i·mous</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Recumbent
</word>
<def>lying down; reclining; leaning.</def>
<pron>re·cum·bent</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Stratagem
</word>
<def>a plan, scheme, or trick for surprising or deceiving an enemy.</def>
<pron>strat·a·gem</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Acuity
</word>
<def>Sharpness or keenness of thought, vision, or hearing.</def>
<pron>a·cu·i·ty</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Delineate
</word>
<def>to trace the outline of; sketch or trace in outline; represent pictorially: He delineated the state of Texas on the map with a red pencil.</def>
<pron>de·lin·e·ate</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Depraved
</word>
<def>Morally corrupt</def>
<pron>de·praved</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Enervate
</word>
<def>to deprive of force or strength; destroy the vigor of; weaken.</def>
<pron>en·er·vate</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Esoteric
</word>
<def>understood by or meant for only the select few who have special knowledge or interest; recondite: poetry full of esoteric allusions.</def>
<pron>es·o·ter·ic</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Fecund
</word>
<def>producing or capable of producing offspring, fruit, vegetation, etc., in abundance; prolific; fruitful: fecund parents; fecund farmland.</def>
<pron>fe·cund</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Fiat
</word>
<def>an authoritative decree, sanction, or order: a royal fiat. Synonyms: authorization, directive, ruling, mandate, diktat, ukase.</def>
<pron>fi·at</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Figment
</word>
<def>a mere product of mental invention; a fantastic notion: The noises in the attic were just a figment of his imagination.</def>
<pron>fig·ment</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Garner
</word>
<def>to gather or deposit in or as if in a granary or other storage place.</def>
<pron>gar·ner</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Hallow
</word>
<def>to make holy; sanctify; consecrate.</def>
<pron>hal·low</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Idiosyncrasy
</word>
<def>a characteristic, habit, mannerism, or the like, that is peculiar to an individual.</def>
<pron>id·i·o·syn·cra·sy</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Ignominy
</word>
<def>Public shame or disgrace: "the ignominy of being imprisoned".</def>
<pron>ig·no·min·y</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Mundane
</word>
<def>Lacking interest or excitement; dull. Of this earthly world rather than a heavenly or spiritual one..</def>
<pron>mun·dane</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Nuance
</word>
<def>a subtle difference or distinction in expression, meaning, response, etc.</def>
<pron>nu·ance</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Overweening
</word>
<def>presumptuously conceited, overconfident, or proud: a brash, insolent, overweening fellow.</def>
<pron>o·ver·ween·ing</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Penchant
</word>
<def>A strong or habitual liking for something or tendency to do something</def>
<pron>pen·chant</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Reputed
</word>
<def>estimation in the view of others; reputation: persons of good repute.</def>
<pron>re·put·ed</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Sophistry
</word>
<def>The use of fallacious arguments, esp. with the intention of deceiving.A fallacious argument.</def>
<pron>soph·ist·ry</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Sumptuous
</word>
<def>entailing great expense, as from choice materials, fine work, etc.; costly: a sumptuous residence.</def>
<pron>sump·tu·ous</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Ubiquitous
</word>
<def>Present, appearing, or found everywhere: "his ubiquitous influence".</def>
<pron>u·biq·ui·tous</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Abject
</word>
<def>utterly hopeless, miserable, humiliating, or wretched: abject poverty.</def>
<pron>ab·ject</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Agnostic
</word>
<def>\the essential nature of things are unknown and unknowable, or that human knowledge is limited to experience.</def>
<pron>ag·nos·tic</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Complicity
</word>
<def>The state of being involved with others in an illegal activity or wrongdoing</def>
<pron>com·plic·i·ty</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Derelict
</word>
<def>left or deserted, as by the owner or guardian; abandoned: a derelict ship.</def>
<pron>der·e·lict</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Diatribe
</word>
<def>A forceful and bitter verbal attack against someone or something.</def>
<pron>di·a·tribe</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Effigy
</word>
<def>a representation or image, especially sculptured, as on a monument.</def>
<pron>ef·fi·gy</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Equity
</word>
<def>the quality of being fair or impartial; fairness; impartiality: the equity of Solomon. Synonyms: disinterest, equitableness, impartiality, fair-mindedness, fairness, justness, evenhandedness, objectivity; justice, probity. Antonyms: bias, discrimination, inequity, injustice, partiality, partisanship, prejudice, unfairness, unreasonableness; injustice.</def>
<pron>eq·ui·ty</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Inane
</word>
<def>lacking sense, significance, or ideas; silly: inane questions.</def>
<pron>in·ane</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Indictment
</word>
<def>an act of indicting.</def>
<pron>in·dict·ment</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Indubitable
</word>
<def>Impossible to doubt; unquestionable: "an indubitable truth"</def>
<pron>in·du·bi·ta·ble</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Intermittent
</word>
<def>stopping or ceasing for a time; alternately ceasing and beginning again: an intermittent pain.</def>
<pron>in·ter·mit·tent</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Moot
</word>
<def>open to discussion or debate; debatable; doubtful: a moot point.</def>
<pron>moot</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Motif
</word>
<def>a recurring subject, theme, idea, etc., especially in a literary, artistic, or musical work.</def>
<pron>mo·tif</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Neophyte
</word>
<def>a beginner or novice: He's a neophyte at chess.</def>
<pron>ne·o·phyte</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Perspicacity
</word>
<def>keenness of mental perception and understanding; discernment; penetration.</def>
<pron>per·spi·cac·i·ty</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Plenary
</word>
<def>full; complete; entire; absolute; unqualified: plenary powers.</def>
<pron>ple·na·ry</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Surveillance
</word>
<def>a watch kept over a person, group, etc., especially over a suspect, prisoner, or the like: The suspects were under police surveillance.</def>
<pron>sur·veil·lance</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Sylvan
</word>
<def>of, pertaining to, or inhabiting the woods.</def>
<pron>syl·van</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Testy
</word>
<def>Easily irritated; impatient and somewhat bad-tempered</def>
<pron>tes·ty</pron>
</SATWord>
<SATWord>
<word>Travesty
</word>
<def>a literary or artistic burlesque of a serious work or subject, characterized by grotesque or ludicrous incongruity of style, treatment, or subject matter.</def>
<pron>trav·es·ty</pron>
</SATWord>
</SATWordList>
