<SATWordList>
    <SATWord>
        <word>Abject
        </word>
        <def>utterly hopeless, miserable, humiliating, or wretched: abject poverty.</def>
        <pron>ab·ject</pron>
    </SATWord>
    <SATWord>
        <word>Agnostic
        </word>
        <def>a person who holds that the existence of the ultimate cause, as God, and the essential nature of things are unknown and unknowable, or that human knowledge is limited to experience. Synonyms: disbeliever, nonbeliever, unbeliever; doubter, skeptic, secularist, empiricist; heathen, heretic, infidel, pagan.</def>
        <pron>ag·nos·tic</pron>
    </SATWord>
    <SATWord>
        <word>Complicity</word>
        <def>The state of being involved with others in an illegal activity or wrongdoing.</def>
        <pron>com·plic·i·ty</pron>
    </SATWord>
    <SATWord>
        <word>Derelict
        </word>
        <def>left or deserted, as by the owner or guardian; abandoned: a derelict ship.</def>
        <pron>der·e·lict</pron>
    </SATWord>
    <SATWord>
        <word>Diatribe
        </word>
        <def>A forceful and bitter verbal attack against someone or something.</def>
        <pron>di·a·tribe</pron>
    </SATWord>
    <SATWord>
        <word>Effigy
        </word>
        <def>a representation or image, especially sculptured, as on a monument.</def>
        <pron>ef·fi·gy</pron>
    </SATWord>
    <SATWord>
        <word>Equity
        </word>
        <def>the quality of being fair or impartial; fairness; impartiality: the equity of Solomon. Synonyms: disinterest, equitableness, impartiality, fair-mindedness, fairness, justness, evenhandedness, objectivity; justice, probity. Antonyms: bias, discrimination, inequity, injustice, partiality, partisanship, prejudice, unfairness, unreasonableness; injustice.</def>
        <pron>eq·ui·ty</pron>
    </SATWord>
    <SATWord>
        <word>Inane
        </word>
        <def>lacking sense, significance, or ideas; silly: inane questions.</def>
        <pron>in·ane</pron>
    </SATWord>
    <SATWord>
        <word>Indictment</word>
        <def>A formal charge or accusation of a serious crime: "an indictment for conspiracy".</def>
        <pron>in·dict·ment</pron>
    </SATWord>
    <SATWord>
        <word>Indubitable</word>
        <def>Impossible to doubt; unquestionable: "an indubitable truth"</def>
        <pron>in·du·bi·ta·ble</pron>
    </SATWord>
    <SATWord>
        <word>Intermittent
        </word>
        <def>stopping or ceasing for a time; alternately ceasing and beginning again: an intermittent pain.</def>
        <pron>in·ter·mit·tent</pron>
    </SATWord>
    <SATWord>
        <word>Moot
        </word>
        <def>open to discussion or debate; debatable; doubtful: a moot point.</def>
        <pron>moot</pron>
    </SATWord>
    <SATWord>
        <word>Motif
        </word>
        <def>a recurring subject, theme, idea, etc., especially in a literary, artistic, or musical work.</def>
        <pron>mo·tif</pron>
    </SATWord>
    <SATWord>
        <word>Neophyte
        </word>
        <def>a beginner or novice: He's a neophyte at chess.</def>
        <pron>ne·o·phyte</pron>
    </SATWord>
    <SATWord>
        <word>Perspicacity
        </word>
        <def>keenness of mental perception and understanding; discernment; penetration.</def>
        <pron>per·spi·cac·i·ty</pron>
    </SATWord>
    <SATWord>
        <word>Plenary
        </word>
        <def>full; complete; entire; absolute; unqualified: plenary powers.</def>
        <pron>ple·na·ry</pron>
    </SATWord>
    <SATWord>
        <word>Surveillance
        </word>
        <def>a watch kept over a person, group, etc., especially over a suspect, prisoner, or the like: The suspects were under police surveillance.</def>
        <pron>sur·veil·lance</pron>
    </SATWord>
    <SATWord>
        <word>Sylvan
        </word>
        <def>of, pertaining to, or inhabiting the woods.</def>
        <pron>syl·van</pron>
    </SATWord>
    <SATWord>
        <word>Testy
        </word>
        <def>Easily irritated; impatient and somewhat bad-tempered</def>
        <pron>tes·ty</pron>
    </SATWord>
    <SATWord>
        <word>Travesty
        </word>
        <def>a literary or artistic burlesque of a serious work or subject, characterized by grotesque or ludicrous incongruity of style, treatment, or subject matter.</def>
        <pron>trav·es·ty</pron>
    </SATWord>
</SATWordList>
